a guy came from the Russian Federation and
пришёл чувак из Российской Федерации и
made your dad some kind of
поставил вашего папу каким-то
commandant
комендантом
of Kramatorsk Yes, but there were already people there before my father,
Краматорска Да но до моего отца там уже
I know that he
были люди я знаю что он с ним
called him and was subordinate to him,
созванивался да и был в его подчинении
this is a fact I understand yes And on what basis is
это факт понял да А на каком основании
Girkin who was such a
гиркин кто вообще был такой
Girkin  good afternoon Hello Good
гиркин добрый день Здравствуйте Добрый
evening or rather I constantly I
вечер точнее я постоянно Я весь день
say good all day long Night good night yes
говорю добрый уже Ночь добрый ночи да
dadada here
дадада вот
What is your name Andrey My name is Alexey
Как вас зовут Андрей Меня зовут Алексей
Where is this city from?  Khmelnitsky And you, I am
Вы откуда город Хмельницкий А вы я
Russia Kostroma and Khmelnitsky
Россия Кострома а Хмельницкий
Khmelnitsky - what is the region of
Хмельницкий - это какая область
Khmelny region of dadada Sorry, I’m in
хмельни область дадада Простите я в
geography between Starokonstantinov and
географии между староконстантинова и
Ermolin, I say I’m very bad in geography,
ермолин я говорю я в географии очень
it didn’t give me anything Sorry, well,
плохо мне это ничего не дало Извините ну
Oh, then between Volovo and
Ой тогда между волоком и
Tim Okay, I understood poorly, very poorly
Тим Ладно я понял плохо очень плохо
Sorry ok Yes, I understand how you are doing. And
Извините окей Да понял как у вас дела А
Kostroma This is where Kostroma is - this is
Кострома Это где Кострома - это вот
St. Petersburg and Moscow  between them,
санктпетербург и Москва вот между ними
closer to Moscow Yeah, I understood everything Well, again,
ближе к Москве Ага понял всё Ну опять же
I didn’t know this until I came here And I
Я этого не знал пока сюда не приехал А я
didn’t know that Well, from Kramatorsk And that’s
не знал что Ну да из Краматорска А
cool How long ago did you come from
прикольно А как Вы давно приехали из
Kramatorsk in 2014 That’s cool, and what
Краматорска в 2014 Прикольно да а что
happened that you left Kramatorsk
случилось что вы уехали из Краматорска
Arrivals in Kramatorsk began
начались прилёты по краматорску понял
Well, wait, how come you don’t remember
месяц Ну подождите как это вы не помните
when we left? It’s around June. It was
когда выехали это июнь примерно Был
probably Inya, but on June 17th my
наверное Иня вот 17 июня мне
wife told me, she remembered it better than I did, Ponya.
жена она запомнила лучше чем я да Поня А
What happened there in Kramatorsk, that there were
что там случилось в Краматорске у вас
arrivals there, I don’t know
такое что там прилёты пошли я не знаю
why the arrivals took place right away?
изза чего прилёты прошли я сразу же
say proactively, I can
упреждающий говори я вот можете
say that this is from the Russian side
утверждать что это с российской стороны
or the Ukrainian side. I don’t know. No, what about you,
или украинской Я не знаю Нет а что вас
what happened in Slavyansk and
там что у вас происходило в Славянске и
Kramatorsk, just this  I
Краматорске как раз вот это славянски
can’t say it in Slavic E because I wasn’t there
сказать не могу Э потому что я там не
I will speak from the point of view of
был я буду говорить от точки зрения того
what I heard I saw in Kramatorsk
что то что я слышал я ви в Краматорске
like what you had, what
типа что у вас было что у вас
happened in the sirens Well, before
происходило в сирен Ну перед тем как
after, more precisely, how the planes flew,
после точнее того как летали самолёты ну
okay  They flew and flew
ладно летали и летали
and the siren started, most likely the jammers turned on
а началась сирена включились скорее
Because I couldn’t
всего глушилки Потому что я не мог
get through to my wife to say that
дозвониться до жены сказать что со мной
everything was fine with me, I was already running and I heard a
всё в порядке я уже бегу и я услышал
terrible roar that I had never heard
жуткий грохот который не слышал никогда
in my life so super  When did this
в жизни так супер Когда это было что это
happen, when did this happen? I said it
случилось когда так Я же сказал это
turns out in June, it was because we
получается в июне было потому что мы
literally left a few days later,
буквально через несколько дней мы уехали
I just see that from April 12,
просто я вот смотрю что вот с 12 апреля
Yes,
Да
until when, until July 5, Yes, Kramatorsk was
по когда по 5 июля Да Краматорск был
occupied by these shooters Yes, by
оккупирован вот этими стрелков Да
Russian militants  Well, if from the point of
российскими боевиками Ну если с точки
view of your rhetoric, then yes it turns out yes. Well, from the point of view, from the point of view of your
как с точки з с точки зрения вашей
rhetoric, the points of your rhetoric. And from the point of view of your rhetoric,
риторики точки вашей риторики А с точки
what happened from the point of view of my
вашей риторики что было с с точки моей
rhetoric, it was not  occupied
риторики это было не оккупирована
and people expressed their opinion at the beginning Look,
а люди выразили своё мнение нач Смотри
right now, not far from Kostroma, it’s like this.
вот сейчас недалеко от Костромы так есть
E, this is a pre-trial detention center in Moscow, and now
Э это СИЗО такое в Москве да там сейчас
I’m wildly sorry, please, I’m still the same.
я дико извиняюсь пожалуйста Я снко ещё
Sorry, can I eat there and eat eat? Let’s
та Извините можно я там буду кушать и
eat, thank you very much
жри жри Давай жри спасибо большое потому
because I really want to insult  if anything Yes,
что очень хочу оскорбить если что Да вот
look, there was such a shooter Yes, who
смотри вот был такой стрелков Да который
captured Kramatorsk and Slavyansk there, so
захватил там Краматорск и Славянск так
no no He took Slavyansk, this is a fact
нет нет Он Славянск взял это факт
Slavyansk  Who took Kramatorsk? My father,
Славянск Кто взял Краматорск э Мой отец
who is your
кто ваш
father? Well, let me not name it,
отец Ну давайте я не буду называть
because it’s like, look at his head again and
потому что за его голову как бы не ещё
again, everyone who was moving there, a
раз смотрите все кто там движе ли уже
long time ago,
давным-давно
like they were tugging, like yes, I don’t understand. I
типа дёргали типа да вот Я не понял В
mean, they were tugging, what does that mean? Well  They have
смысле дёргали что это значит Ну нашли
already found everyone
уже всех
who is not found, but it turns out they weren’t found.
кто нет не нашли но получается не нашли
Because my father was the commandant
Потому что мой отец был комендантом
of Kramatorsk,
Краматорска вот
uh, this is the one from Dnepropetrovsk.
Ээ это тот что с Днепропетровска гин
Excuse me for a second, he’s
Извините меня на секундочку он арестован
already arrested in the Russian Federation, which means  they didn’t
уже в Российской Федерации значит не
find him in Russia under Look, they didn’t
нашли его в Росси уне подо Смотри не его
just find him, He ran away, so look,
нашли просто Он убежал так вот смотри
tell me how you look, look, you’re
расскажи мне как у как Смотри ты ты тут
here, you know, you don’t know when your dad
тут Знаешь тут не знаешь когда твой папа
Yes, he became the commandant there of Kramatorsk
Да взял стал комендантом там Краматорска
No, I know exactly when I know, I don’t
Нет я знаю точно когда я знаю не надо
need  present such a moment that this is a
мне предъявлять такой момент что вот
psychological moment about the fact
психологический такой момент насчёт того
that I know I don’t know I know that it was
что знаю не знаю я знаю что это было
summer it all started Excuse me since
лето началось всё Извините меня с
2013 the summer has already
2013 летом уже
ended in the summer it all
закончилось краматорс летом всё
ended started in  April in
закончилось началось в апреле в
Kramatorsk it all started. I mean in the
Краматорске началось Всё я имею в виду в
country and not in Kramatorsk. And if we
стране а не в Краматорске А если мы
are talking about Kramatorsk. Yes,
говорим про Краматорск Да вполне воз
you can ask so that the pots don’t
можешь попросить чтобы кастрюлями не
rattle, it’s not her that’s distracting;
гремела то отвлекает это не она это я не
stop
чтобы Таня Короче я могу перестать
eating dumplings honestly so as not to eat You
кушать пельмешки честно чтобы не ть Ты
eat eat Yes you Thank you Thank you
кушай кушай Да ти Спасибо Спасибо
very much then if your dad was
большое то если твой папа был
the commandant of Kramatorsk when he became the
комендантом Краматорска когда он стал
commandant
комендантом
Kramatorsk Well, starting from spring Yes, yes,
Краматорска Ну начиная с весны Да да я
I have to lead a certain family in the family,
что я в семье должен вести определённый
like, well, you were in Kramatorsk, you
как бы ну вы в Краматорске вы в
lived there in Kramatorsk, for example. Well,
Краматорске там жили например Ну
explain, Yes, I lived in Kramatorsk for
объясните
20 years, you lived
Да я 20 лет прожил в Краматорске вы жили
in Kramatorsk, Yes, your dad. Who was he in
в Краматорске Да ваш папа Кем был в
Kramatorsk, what did he become?  the commandant who
Краматорске что он стал комендантом кто
appointed him the commandant of Kramatorsk was
его назначил комендантом Краматорска
specifically
конкретно
Girkin, that is, look who Girkin
гиркин то есть Смотри кто такой гиркин
was I don’t know such a
был Я хз такой
person adj dude from  Russian Federation
чело прил чувак из Российской Федерации
and made your dad some kind of
и поставил вашего папу каким-то
commandant, the
комендантом
krator
кратор до мого
kept repeating in his own words until then. It’s not me. That
отже твердил своими словами Не я Что
Irkin, but we
Иркин Да вот российский какой-то мы
won’t be some kind of Russian now. Who is he from Russia who came
сейчас не будем Кто он из России пришёл
and understood? No, the question is that this is my
и понял Нет не вопрос в том что это моё
assumption. I don’t know.  you You clearly
предположение Я не знаю ты Ты чётко
said that your dad was installed by Girkin
сказал что твоего папу поставил гиркин
It was I who said I said, please note that
Это я сказал я сказал вот прошу заметить
I said and not my father or Girkin said
я сказал а не мой отец или гиркин сказал
that he installed it This is my
что он его поставил Это моё
assumption that it was so, I know that he is
предположение что так было я знаю что он
with him  called up and was subordinate to him,
с ним созванивался да и был в его
that’s a fact, yes And on what basis
подчинении это факт да А на каком основа
was Girkin, who was such a
гиркин кто вообще был такой гиркин да
Girkin in the first place? The devil knows there was such confusion there, well, wait, Well, who was such a Girkin, that he appointed someone in your city, something
гиркин что он в вашем городе что-то там
good?  such a question,
кого-то назначал хорошо такой вопрос
if I say that he was the president of
если я скажу что он был президентом
Ukraine, it would be nonsense, right. Well,
Украины это будет же чушь правильно Ну
of course, the nonsense knows who he is. Well,
конечно чуш знает кто это такой Ну так
here comes a man. The question is
вот Вот пришёл человек Он вопрос в том
that he supported people who, well, in
что он поддержал людей которые Ну в
Kharkov  taken out And in the Donetsk
Харькове не вывезли А в Донецкой
Lugansk region they took out our weapons
Луганской области они вывезли наш оружие
like this and the people there didn’t take them out there they
как это а люди там не вывезли там
took them out. What kind of guest performers,
вывезли Это что за гастролёры
well, damn, I can’t find another term, like the
ну ну блин я другого термина не могу
one you said,
найти вот как который вы сказали
some kind of guest performers weren’t taken out in
гастролёры какие-то вот не вывезли в
Kharkov But in Donetsk and  For
Харькове Но в Донецке и Луганске
some reason they took them out of Lugansk, they found
почему-то вывезли нашли
weapons, it turns out that the Russians Yes, they
оружие получается что россияне Да
organized a movement there. Yes, no, I think
устроили э там Движуху Да нет я думаю
that the Russians simply supported it, otherwise
что россияне просто поддержали иначе бы
if  that they are there You said that
если го что они там Ты же сказал что
some guest performers supported
какие-то гастролёры ну как поддержали
him so well Look who was who was and the commandant of
Смотри кто был кто был да комендантом
this
этого
Slavyansk I don’t know, well, probably
Славянска Я не знаю ну в стно наверно
shooters
стрелков
Girkin, that is, he is some kind of This
гиркин то есть и он какой-то Этот
Russian man and from Russia, a citizen of the
русский мужик да из России гражданин
Russian Federation appointed everyone  these are
Российской Федерации назначал всех этих
your dads there in short and so Dada exactly like
вашего папу там короче и так Дада именно
that And on what basis exactly did this
так А на каком основании именно вот этот
guy from Russia appoint your Popes,
мужик из России назначал ваших Пап я вот
that’s why I said when you said
поэтому и сказал когда Вы заявили насчёт
that  tourers, I can call
того что гастролёры я по-другому назвать
it differently and I
это и
don’t like the fact that people
негу то что люди
stood up so that Woo would come in. They would have
поднялись те чтобы ву заходила Их бы
simply been gouged out but they came. These are the
просто раздолбали но пришли Вот такие
tourers you call Girkin and so
гастролёры вы называете гиркин и так
on and organized it, that is, it also
далее и организовали это то есть ещ
turns out that you are now
получается вы сейчас
confirming your words and that some
подтверждаете свои слова да что какие-то
people  they came from Russia yes and they
люди пришли из России да и сделали там
seized territories there
захват территорий
no they organized they helped organize the
нет организовали помогли Организовать
defense Yes again what did they
оборону Да ещ раз что они
raise and help or were they
подняли и помогли или они были
the leaders of this whole thing No they helped
руководителями этой всей Нет они помогли
It’s good if they helped whom they
Хорошо если они помогли кому они
helped  Give the name to whom they
помогали Назовите фамилию кому они
obeyed Who led them, those who
подчинялись Кто ими руководил те те кто
came to help No, let’s Who was in
приехал помогать Не ну к Давайте Кто был
charge in all this No, well, you’re a
главный в этом всём Не ну ну вы же
logical person, you understand that you can’t
логичный человек вы понимаете что нельзя
name one person, but I don’t know
называть одного человека вот я не знаю
how, but Putin is to blame and that’s all Well,
как вот вот Путин виноват и всё Ну
for example  Look, here comes the shooters
например смотри вот приезжает стрелков
Yes, and he says he takes someone, for example,
Да и говорит берёт какого-то например
so this is a media personality, and not
так это ж медийная личность та там не
only was Gir Girkin there. Well, he takes trees and sticks, he
только был Гир гиркин Ну ёлки-палки он
takes someone from Kramatorsk by
берёт берёт какого-то с Краматорска по
name  Why exactly
имени Почему именно
why is it burning Gena you will be
почему почему горит Гена ты будешь
shorter with this uh commandant are you serious you
короче этим ээ комендант вы серьёзно вы
think that in Kramatorsk there is only one Well
думаете что в Краматорске только есть Ну
yes we saw this Gennady Kim
да мы видели вот этот Геннадий Ким
whom he appointed
которого назначил он
was he involved in yes oh Christmas trees Well do
был ли занимался да ох ёлки Ну да вы что
n’t you know him
не знаете его
This is my father so yes  Well, it can’t
Это мой отец так да Ну не может
be, but he was involved in trade, but
быть да вот торговле он занимался но
obviously not. Why was he involved in alcohol? Yes,
явно не Ну почему алкоголем алкоголем
yes he was involved in alcohol. Yes,
да да занимался Да он
by the way, in Dnepropetrovsk, he then kept a
кстати в Днепропетровске он тогда держал
type under the auspices of
типа под эгидой
Let’s have a military-patriotic club, so
Давайте клуб военно-патриотический так у
he didn’t have that  was If he were in
него был не было такого был Был бы он в
Kramatorsk he was in the Cossacks it was but
Краматорске был в казачестве это было но
in Dnepropetrovsk there was no such thing about
в Днепропетровске такого не было спро
Dnepropetrovsk he worked in a company
Днепропетровский он работал в компании
that supplied elite alcohol to
которая поставляла элитный алкоголь в
Ukraine the only company Yes
Украину единственная компания Да
Ask your dad about this
Спросишь у папы да про этот
military-patriotic club in
военно-патриотический клуб в
Dnepropetrovsk by the way Dnepropetrovsk is an
днепропетровс кстати Днепропетровск
amazing day now  day Yes
потрясающий голов дне сейчас дне Да
You ask
Спросишь у
dad What happened to dad now This is
папы Что сейчас с папой случилось Вот
where
где сейчас
dad is fighting now
папа воюет
Where at the front Yes and why is he  Look,
Где на фронте Да а почему он Смотри вот
he sent his son to Russia to
он своего сыночка отправил в Россию в
Kostroma Uga So he didn’t leave the
Кострому Угу Так а не оставил чтобы вот
young DPR over there to
вон ДНР молодую Республику что-то
defend something. But here’s a question for a second,
защищать А вот вопрос на секундочку вот
your child will be captured, what
ваш ребёнок попадёт в плен вы что
will you do no no look again, no no no
сделаете нет нет ещё раз смотрите вот ва
no  This is a specific question,
нет нет не нет Вот это конкретный вопрос
your child will get caught again,
вот ваш ребёнок попадёт ещё раз ещё раз
look again, no, no, no need to throw facts around like that,
смотри не не не надо вот так вот фактами
sends, look with my
перекидывать отправляет смотри с моим
father, if they give nothing for his head, that’s it
отцом если за его голову дают вот ничего
oh-oh-oh there are so many thousands of people there.
себе ой-ой-ой там сколько тысяч до Вот
You should be sitting at the headquarters in Donetsk, here you
вы бы сидели в штабе в Донецке вот в
are sitting at the headquarters so that they don’t take you prisoner.
штабе сидели да чтоб вас в плен не взяли
Well, maybe a missile will fly in. Why are the
Ну вот может ракета прилететь Почему
guys from Kramatorsk from Oh, not from
ребят из Краматорска из Ой не из
Kramatorsk? Free the guys from
Краматорска Освободи уже ребята из
Donetsk already! Yes from  Gorlovka is forcibly mobiles are
Донецка Да из Горловки насильно мобили
thrown like living goals from where
зру ет кидают как живые голы откуда
mobiles are from Gorlovka from Donetsk and so
мобили из Горловки из Донецка и так
on and it sits and dad sent you Kost
да а высиживает А вас папа отправил Кост
sit out Well, I tried to explain to you right away,
отсидеться Ну так я же пытался Вам сразу
imagine you have
объяснить вот Представьте У вас есть
a child, he ends up in the enemy
ребёнок он попадает во вражескую службу
FSB service, let’s assume what I will do with him and what
ФСБ предположим что с ним сделаю и что
you will do in order to
вы сделаете для того чтобы ребёнка
free your child. That is, you want to say it
освободить То есть вы хотите сказать ещё
again, not just once again, you understand that I
раз не ещё раз Вы поймите что я хотел
wanted wanted to go I had the intention of going
хотел пойти у меня было намерение пойти
to Girki so for the
к гирки так для
same thing No votcha no it’s like ki that’s the name
тогоже Нет вотча нет это как ки вот имен
that time and it happened when Birkin was
то время и случилось когда биркин был
still and and he told you in Kostroma Well,
ещё а и вас сказал в Кострому Ну вообще
not there at all But this is for  what I'm
не туда Но это для того что я
guessing to confuse, and that is, it
предполагаю запутать а то есть
turns out I understood, that is, in the fourteenth
получается понял то есть в четырнадцатом
year, and when, uh, in Kramatorsk,
году да когда ээ в Краматорске славянски
these Russians got Slavic stars Yes, they
получили звездюлей эти россияне Да они
all turned out there Yes, your your dad is
все сли получились там Да ваш ваш папа
somewhere in Donetsk or Gorlovka there,
где-то в Донецк или в Горловку там спе
first of all, there were no Persians there  at that
вопервых персиан там не было на тот
moment for a second e Well, how was there no
момент на секундочку е Ну как не было
motoro motoro the Russian was no no
моторо моторо россиянин был нет нет
he was motoro from Wow, what a Ukrainian Yes
он моторо из Ух ты какой украинский Да
he is Slavic You  Are you kidding me?
он Славянский Вы что издеваетесь что
Look now, dude, you know why
посмотри Сейчас чувак знаете почему
he’s wearing Motorola because he’s
моторол он потому что
Moro, let’s just look at this. Come on now,
Моро давай так вот смотри Давай сейчас
let Tanya take your wife and look at
пусть Таня твоя жена возьмёт и посмотри
this. Let’s touch my
се Давайте трогать мою
wife because you’re
жену потому что вот Вы такими
manipulating such moments of
манипулирую моментами
interest. Let’s let your wife
интерес Давайте вашу жену возм дава
look at the phone.
се пусть она возм телефон посмотрит
where was Mola from? Mola from the city of Ukhta is
откуда был Мола Мола из города Ухта сла
not famous Slavyansk Look now I
не Славянска Вот посмотри Сейчас я
admit that he is nice I’m here now
признаю что он славн я вот
I admit that I’m wrong, okay
сечас я признаю что я не прав хорошо
Mola How Donbass is
Мола Как Донбасс
probably a motor biography, take for example
наверно моторо биография возьми например
Arsen Sergeevich what is
Арсен Сергеевич что это
it This is a motor
такое Это моторо
participant in the armed conflict in
участник вооружённого конфликта на
eastern Ukraine, the commander
востоке Украины командир
of an anti-tank And even an anti-tank is
противотанкового А даже противотанкового
interesting in a special unit of
интересно специального подразделения
Sparta Well, it looks like the truth Donetsk
Спарта Ну похоже на правду Донецкий
People’s Republic so Give me the
народной Республики так Отдайте мне
full where is he?
полную где он
Donetsk Ukraine is his wife Although
что Донецк Украина это его супруга Хотя
Well, yes, in
Ну да в
principle, that’s how he was born in the third Ukhta
принципе так родился в во третьем Ухта А
Well, Ukhta Well, the USSR, yes he worked as a redneck or
ну Ухта Ну СССР да работал краснода или
somewhere there on a car 2002 And I’m
где-то там на автомо 2002 Причём я это
looking at this in And now for a second I’ll
смотрю в А сейчас на секундочку я сейчас
fix it all and send you a screenshot
это Всё исправлю и скриншот вам скину
because it’s like Wikipedia Yes,
потому что это что Википедия Да её
anyone who wants can edit it yes Well,
править может любой кто хочет да Ну
look, find it’s not Wikipedia Find somewhere else
смотри найти не Википедии Найди в другое
where it is Well, if  he is from Slavyansk there
где он Ну если он из Славянска там куча
should be a lot of information and I was born in
должна быть информация а я родился в
Yekaterinburg and it turns out that my
Екатеринбурге и что я получается моя
wound was further biography Read Okay
рана была дальше биографию Почитай Ладно
ok Well  where is he from? Where is he?
хорошо Ну откуда он Где он бы
No, I need a biography specifically. 2002
Нет мне нужна биография конкретно 2002
left Ukhta and became a resident to serve in the
покинул Ухту и стал жителем служить
Russian armed forces. Well, okay, he served for 3 years.
вооруженных силах России Ну окей 3 года
Well, that doesn’t give me anything. 7th
служил Ну это мне ничего не даёт 7
Marine Corps as a Szi Yes, that’s where his
морской пехоты как сзи Да отсюда Его
nickname came from. He completed the
прозвище пришёл что а Прошёл курс
initial lifeguard training course in
начальной подготовки спасателя в
Krasnodar  training center Ral
Краснодарском учебном центре Раль
against him Indicated the possession of such
проти же он Обозначил владение такими
professions Well, professions are not important to me
професси Ну мне профессии не важны
Lord On March 15, 2012, on October 15, 2012, by the court on
Господи 15 марта 2012 октября судом на
the height of the Don, together with a certain Denisenko,
ростом Дону совместно с неким Денисенко
he was given probation  sentenced to imprisonment
был условно приговорён лишению Свободы
Well, that is, you are hinting that he is a
Ну то есть вы намекаете что это он
criminal, not yet what year
уголовник нене ещё ты про какой год
did you read about that Well, on March 15, 2012, the
прочитал что Ну вот 15 марта 2012 год та
same Wikipedia which which court m the
же Википедия каким каким судом м
October court of Rostov will need to Rostov will
октябрьским судом Ростова надону Ростова
need to That is, he lived in Rostov, that
надону То есть он жил в Ростове ну то
is, not in  Slavyansk Well, damn Putin
есть не в Славянске Ну блин Путина
was sentenced Excuse me
приговорили Извините меня международным
internationally, we are guilty now you just read with your own
сум винова мы сейчас ты сейчас своими
lips that it turns out Arsen
губами прочитал что оказывается Арсен
Pavlov  motor catchers,
Павлов мотороловцы
I haven’t heard this, but it’s interesting that
я вот этого не слышал но интересно вот
Dana gets a year and a half for stealing a car Wow,
Дане на полтора года за угон автомобиля
that’s an interesting biography without the purpose of
Ух ты интересная биография без целе
theft, it’s like without the purpose of theft at all, it’s
хищения это как вообще без цели хищения
interesting the theft from the car
интересно хищение с автома на которой
they worked on. According to Well, damn it, I’m
они работали Согласно Ну блин здесь
just waiting here to get citizenship, just give
жда вобью просто гражданство давай
it to me  also Wikipedia Well, at least tell me
Ну мне тоже Википедия Ну так вы мне хоть
Wikipedia
Википедия
doesn’t load like that, sad new gazeta.ru Have
так не грузится печально новая gazeta.ru
you cut off my Internet or something? It’s
Вы что мне интернет обрубили что ли Это
just a joke on you  the guys have already left, the
шутка за тобой просто выехали уже
class is good.
ребят класс хорошо
In the sense of SSb or
В смысле ссб или
SB And this is the same thing
СБ А это же Одно и тоже
with SB, this is exactly in your understanding class
с СБ это прям в вашем понимании класс
Ache will touch you exactly
Аче трогать будет тебя
where the steam will go
точи откуда паро поедем
next. Damn, should I launch Yandex, I don’t
дальше Да блин Яндекс ли запустить я не
know that it’s not Georgians
знаю что тут не грузин
loading so
грузится так
cool
здорово
Donetsk
Донецк
citizenship  so YouTube or damn it, I did
гражданство так YouTube не то блин я
n’t even know what a motorol looks like on a horse
даже не знал как моторол выглядит коне
Alexey Gennadievich, in short, you
Алексей Геннадьевич ты короче по истории
don’t know anything about history Dener, yes, yes, I
Денер вообще ничего не знаешь да да я
can also tell you that you are about history  you do
могу тоже вам сказать что вы по истории
n’t know because this is a psychological
не знаете потому что это психологический
technique And now I’m using a psychological technique
приём И сейчас я психологическим приёмом
yes Here we are now Arseniy Pavlo Arseniy
да Вот мы сейчас арсени Павло Арсений
Pavlo motoro
Павло моторо
Yes, he was not from Ukraine Yes, well, I’m not
Да не из Украины был Да ну и я тоже не
from Ukraine either I was born in the Soviet Union,
из Украины Я родился в Советском Союзе
then it’s not like he was born, he
дальше так он не то что родился он
didn’t live at all  in Ukraine Okay and Well, stop,
вообще не жил в Украине Окей и Ну стоп
let me
да давайте я
try. Let me just admit, I
попытаюсь Давайте я просто признаю я
admit, if I
признаю если я
find information, I recognize that I am a participant in the
найду информацию я признаю участник
armed conflict, so Well,
вооруженного конфликта так Ну а
citizenship Well, don’t
гражданство Ну гражданство не
write citizenship to this Yes, well  why are you letting your snot out here,
пишете этому Да ну что вы сопли здесь
childhood is blue, and you are straight
пускаете детство синий это а вас прям
Stream, yes, they are telling you, I see Neda is
Стрим да вам подсказывают я вижу Неде
being told, I just
подсказывают Я тут короче
googled your dad right now, yes, or is it
сейчас папу твоего загуглил да Или это
really? Well, yes, this is my father. They
действительно Ну да Это мой отец Как раз
just showed him. Yes, I wanted not to say, but
таки его показали Да хотел не говорить а
what difference does it make? Yes  they've already hit
какая разница уже пробили Да уже пробили
you Yes,
тебя Да
that's it, you try
всё ну вы попробуйте
serving in the army getting a Civil
служба в армии получение Гражданский
Prim profession war in Ukraine per
Прим профессии война в Украине пер
Dobrovoltsev I'm starting to despair, by my
Добровольцев Я начинаю отчаиваться по
own admission I had to
собственному признанию приходилось
[music] during my
[музыка]
studies
ждения кур сци
prepared Despite
подготов Несмотря
the ses, I’ll change the rune date of the
сес смну руне дате
information clearly But if he was born and lived
информа чётко Но если он родился и жил
there lived in Slavyansk, it’s not just that they
там жил в Славянске не мне просто уже
show me not a Motorola for a campaign, if he
показывают не моторолу походу если бы он
lived in a lot of information, it would be
жил в куча информации бы это вообще
some other information altogether, it’s as if he’s
какая-то другая информация это как будто
not the same
не тот
Materova and people with
матерова и люди с таким интеллектом
In short,
короче
they captured with such intelligence Well, somehow it turned out, apparently
захватывали Ну как-то получилось видимо
the intelligence is present, that they captured or
интеллект присутствует что захватили или
Net the weapons came and Russian and the battle,
Нетто оружие пришло да российское и бое
but Ukraine didn’t want to fight, wanted
а Украина не хотела воевать хотела чтобы
all this to be resolved peacefully, come on  no,
мирно всё это решилось ну давай нет
the question is that it’s a Motorola Find a
вопрос вопрос в том что моторолу Найди
Motorola and we’ll go further than two different
моторолу и поедем дальше двух разных
Motorolas, that’s the thing, some
моторол вот в том-то и дело какой-то
strange guy with a red beard and
непонятный паренёк рыжебородый и как раз
just the same Mola, who is more or less
таки Мола которого вот мне более-менее
fat to me, this is Mola T No, there
жиро это и есть Мола Т Нет ещё другой
was another Mola  Show me some other Motorola
Мола был Покажи какого другого моторолу
How to show you Well, let me
Как тебе показать А ну вот давай я вот
just take off the camera like this and now I see
так камеру просто сниму и вот вот я вижу
this Motorola Now a second a
вот этого моторолу Сейчас секунду
second a second Let's go Like this And you
секунду секунду Давай ть Вот так А ты
like Givi you show
походу Гиви показываешь
Givi this is Givi this is Givi Well Givi looks like
Гиви это Гиви это Гиви Ну Гиви да похож
okay no the question is that Yes
ладно нет вопрос в том что Да я
I can I now understand I now understand that
могу я тепер понял я теперь понял что
your dad sent you to Kostroma
тебя батя в Кострому
because you excuse me
отправил потому что тебя извини меня
let me not joke about such shmi there in
давай не буду я шутить на такие шми там
short In short what  - I just felt like yes, I
короче Короче что-то вчу просто бы да я
felt like that, that is, we have already
вчу бы то есть мы на личности уже
switched to a personal insult Yes,
перешли на оскорбление личностное Да ну
how I have active respect Of course not,
как у меня активо уважения Конечно нет
like I won’t hide it, then come on, so we
типа не буду скрывать то давай так мы
understood that Mola is not  from Ukraine No
поняли что Мола не из Украины Да нет
now you Show that Mola is not from Ukraine
теперь ты Покажи что Мола не из Украины
So you read
Так ты же прочитал
Wikipedia Wikipedia ha
Википедии Википедия ха
Wikipedia koto can only be edited this way
Википедии кото можно править только так
again there are links in Wikipedia Yes
ещё раз там в Википедии есть ссылки Да
no now I was looking Come on you look for it
нет теперь я искал Давай ты ищи
show like that bigra just not from
показывай так бигра только не из
Wikipedia Let's do it
Википедии Давай ещ
again  come on, not from Wikipedia, look on
раз давай не из Википедии смотри в
Wikipedia,
Википедии
listen to that Listen, every sentence
послушай то Слушай в каждом предложении
has a link at the end Come on  I’ll
в конце есть ссылка Давай я тебе сейчас
write you a Wikipedia page now Look, I’m sorry,
страницу Википедии напишу Смотри Извини
I’m also Wikipedia Wikipedia has a link
я тоже Википедии Википедии есть в каждом
at the end of every sentence, you
предложении в конце ссылочка ты
click the footnote and go straight to the
нажимаешь сноску и переходишь прямо на
specific news Yes, look, you’re reading
конкретную новость Да вот смотри читаешь
Tolley I didn’t correct the Wikipedia article
Толи я не правил статьи Википедии ещё
again, so you’re not going to Wikipedia You’re
раз так ты не на Википедию Ты перейдёшь
not going to specifically go to
конкретно не на Википедию ещё раз
Post the link to Wikipedia again, so go here Open it
ссылочку скинь так вот зайди Открой
Wikipedia, I’ll tell you directly that where to
Википедию я тебе прямо скажу что куда
click open Wikipedia Stan
нажать открывай Википедию стани
Pavlova went over So now Find this
Павлова перешёл Так теперь Находи этот
paragraph where you were Deprived of liberty on
абзац где у было Лишение свободы 15
March 15, 2022 so Dada yes Dana now
марта 2022 года се дада да Дана сейчас
so once again what paragraph is there Do you see the
так ещё раз её какой там абзац Видишь
paragraph there March 15, 2012 by the October
там абзац 15 марта 2012 года октябрьским
court no yes  Holy [ __ ], how bad I did
судом нет да Муха как я плохо сделал
everything, come in, I’ll tell you, I
всё зайди Я тебе буду говорить я вот
’ll show you Wikipedia, you see, it’s super,
тебе Википедию показываю видишь супер
look  Open the article, I’ll tell you
смотри Открой статью я тебе скажу на
what link there, click on the article
какую ссылку там перей перешёл по статье
You see it’s written there I see I see you
Видишь там написано Я вижу вижу ты мне
don’t tell me that I’m not
это не рассказывай Я же тебе не
telling you what will be written on
рассказываю что будет написано в
Wikipedia You read at least But I understand
Википеди Ты прочитай хоть А я понимаю
that I see that it’s written
что пере вижу что там типа ки написано
like Go  look, it’s not there, it’s not
типа Зайди смотри не там там не так
written there, it’s written there, go to the page,
написано там написа зайди на страничку
go to the
зайди на страничку
Wikipedia page, there’s a link where to go to
Википедии там есть ссылка куда перейти в
the news on something other than Wikipedia, or do you
новости на не Википедию или ты Ты
seriously think that  we can
серьёзно думаешь что мы можем нормально
already communicate normally if we switched to a
уже пообщаться если Мы перешли на
personal insult, I’m
личность на личностное оскорбление я те
seriously telling you, take it in front of me, I’m
серьёзно говорю возьми переди я тебя
just going to listen to you,
просто аудитори ты
and then you’re like this,
сез а потом такой а
so why are you talking, I’ll
т Так а зачем ты зай разговариваешь я
tell you because I’m interested in
тебе скажу потому что мне интересно с
talking to you, what are
тобой поговорить что
you
тебе тебе
interested in  which Kim
интересно который Ким
said Because you really are the son of this
сказал Потому что ты реально сын этого
Gennady Kim Yes, that’s why I’m having a problem Ira,
Геннадия Кима Да поэтому мне сбой Ире ты
imagine it Yes, really, I’ve
представь себе Да реально я реа
installed it and
установили ре его
I’m interested in I now know that you’re
сы мне интересно Я теперь знаю что ты в
hanging out in castrom, like yes, that’s very
кастроме торчишь типа да это очень
good Yes, we know  That’s what your wife is like. That
хорошо Да знаем Вот то твоя жена типа То
is, you can establish your social contacts.
есть можно твои социальные контакты
That’s very good, now
установить Это очень хорошо а теперь
please try the VPN, which is
пробейте пожалуйста вот VPN который
disabled, that’s where I’m still
отключенный вот где я ещё нахожусь
at all, I do
вообще
n’t care. Well, then you’re still in the campfire. I don’t
пофиг Ну тогда ещё теб в костраме Я не
know, maybe I’m in the language. Well, it doesn’t really matter.
знаю вот Может я в мове Ну это плевать
I don’t care, I don’t care, look about Motorola, I’m done. You
смотри про моторолу закончил Мола ты
admit it, I wasn’t there at all, I don’t admit it. I
признаёшь не был вообще ни не признаю Я
didn’t find any information confirming it. Look
не нашёл информации подтверждающей его
where you go, there
где смотри заходишь вот
’s one, look where you read the books.  I’ll be
есть смотри там где ты читал шки буду
there where you eat the dumpling where you read on
там где жри пельмень там где ты читал в
Wikipedia Yes, about his conviction there is a
Википедии Да вот про его осуждение есть
link directly to the Oktyabrsky District Court of
ссылка прямо на Октябрьский районный суд
the city of Rostov, you need to
города Ростова надону там
eat there and there is this court decision,
есть и там есть это судебное решение
open it so for a second you will come
открой его так на секундочку ты приедешь
to Rostov, I don’t know the person in
в Ростов там я не знаю человек те
Rostov  court, look at this, this is not an
Ростовский суд смотри в этом в это не
argument, that’s what’s the matter there on the
аргумент вот в чём дело там на
citizen This is his citizenship I didn’t find
гражданин Вот это гражданство Я не нашёл
Please find his citizenship I didn’t
Найди пожалуйста гражданство его Я не
find you find it  you will read this in the court decision
нашёл ты найди го в судебном решении ты
But in the court decision
прочитаешь А вот судебном решении Вот
This is some kind of thing I’m telling you, open the
это уже какая-то Я тебе говорю открой
link there, it’s just an unrealistic
ссылке просто нереальный
type, open it at all
тип открывай вообще
Sorry We’ve already switched to Come on, super, you
Извини Мы уже перешли на Давай супер ты
can do what you want Pavlov Asen
можешь что хочешь Павлов Асен
Sergeevich yes, apparently Daro So what’s the
Сергеевич да видимо Даро Так какая
link Let’s find  there is the phrase March 15,
ссылочка Давай находишь там вот фразу 15
March 2012 you see Yes I see but it’s not
марта 2012 года видишь Да вижу но она не
clickable stop no it’s not clickable at the
кликабельна стоп не она не кликабельна в
end of it there’s this in squares  in
конце её там такое в квадратных
parentheses 7 and 8 you see 78 I see yes pressing
скобочках 7 и8 видишь 78 вижу да нажима
and you click on them this and yes Yes, it
и нажимаешь на них се и во да Да так
leads perfectly to the same Wikipedia for No
отлично ведут на ту же Википедию за Не
no no No it
не нет Нет оно оно вниз тебя
went down the links lead you below and there you
опустилось ссылок ведёт внизу и там ты
also see apparently the eighth Yes now
смот также видимо восьмую Да теперь
you click there on the seventh  and on the eighth
нажимаешь там на седьмую и на восьмую
Yeah and you get
Угу и попадаешь
eight on the article so specifically look
восемь на статью так конкретно смотреть
at who I’m clicking on
также на кого я нажимаю
because I really don’t want to figure it all out
по что дофига всех разбираться очень не
So what link are you
хочется Так ну на какую ты ссылку
clicking on  well, a fly, that is, look Find
нажимаешь ну муха то есть смотри Найди
the phrase I found this on March 15, already clicked
фразу Вот это 15 марта нашёл уже перешёл
on the link, here it went down further
по ссылке вот оно спустило вниз дальше
where should I click about you down entered
куда мне нажимать о тебе вниз вступила
this link on what link
на эту ссылку на на какую ссылку Ищенко
Evgeniy Stanislavovich Ishchenko should I click on me or what did
Евгений Станиславович мня нажать или что
you click on Sem and there is this  seventh
ты нажал на Сем и там есть вот седьмое
list of links by numbers you see on
список ссылок по номерам видишь в
Wikipedia look also I see Bednov
Википедии смотреть также вижу беднов
Alexander Aleksandrovich Mozgovoy I’ll click
Александр Александрович мозговой ещё раз
it again  click on the sevens Here you
ё ещё раз нажимаем на семёрочки Вот вы
go there, look above, see
переходим туда же смотри выше смотреть
also what is written and the note you
также что написано а примечание ты
have in the columns above, look here
имеешь колонки выше смотреть вот
October Would you explain at all,
октябр Объясните ли с тебя вообще
of course, thank you, I’m having a hard time discussing so
конечно спасибо я тяжело обс так
judicial regulations,
судебные нормативные акты
here’s the verdict in the name of the Russian Federation
вот приговор именем Российской Федерации
Yes, verdict number one, yes there 10 108
Да приговор номер один да там 10 108
I see Yes, it’s good in the name of the Russian
вижу Да хорошо именем Российской
Federation
Федерации
Rostov Lord again Pavlova where is this
Ростов Господи опять Павлова где это
citizenship please tell me
гражданство ты подскажи
at least the judge is not a judge I have citizenship
хоть судья не судья мне гражданство
Give me a second link Open there  where is
Дайте и вторую ссылку Открой там где
the article about him on your Yes, don’t you
статья про него на вашем Да не ты мне
tell me where the citizenship is written I recognize
скажи где гражданство написано я признаю
e Maybe I could be mistaken then
е Может быть я могу заблуждаться то
Read the court decision Read the
Прочитай судебное решение Прочитай
court decision Let’s read it out loud Sun Let’s read it out loud
судебное решение Давай те вслух ВС Вот
Sun Let’s
это читать давай читай вслух ВС Давай
go to hell I don’t want to I read it out loud read it out
иди нафиг не хочу Я вслух читать почитай
loud  Why is it unrealistic How can I read it out loud
вслух Почему нереально Как я могу вслух
Chita let's read it out loud Well so EU So what are
Чита давай читай вслух Ну так ЕС Так что
you trying to achieve no wait we either
ты добиваешься нет подожди мы либо
talk normally or we
разговариваем нормально либо
talk in mutual
разговариваем на обоюдном
language How how can
языке Как как
we how can we how can we speak
мы как мы можем как мы можем говорить
normally if I’m a normal person from
нормально если я нормальный человек из
Ukraine And you who Why am I I’m from
Украины А ты который Почему я я из
Ukraine just like you you brought
Украины точно так же как и ты ты принёс
about what I didn’t want to be on arrival and
про что я под прилёта не захотел быть а
you’ve never been on arrival  that's all
ты под прилёта ни разу не был вот и всё
You, for example, your dad Yes, they worked for the
Ты ты например твой папа Да работали на
Russians Yes, which I never worked
российских Да которые я не работал
for the Russians I have always been a
никогда на российских Я всегда был
peaceful citizen and peace gram everything yes
мирным гражданином и пацифи грам всё да
yes here is your Daddy Yes sends
да вот и твой Папочка Да отправляет
My father I’ll ask for a second
Мой отец попрошу на секунду
Your yours  Your daddy Daddy is sending
Твой твой Папочка твой Папочка посылает
uh
ээ
people your age Yes, your
людей твоих ровесников Да твоих
peers he knows where you are where he didn’t
ровесников тебя он от знает куда он не
say Sit son in before you’re not for me Prima
сказал Сиди сынок в до ты мне не Прима
We’ll keep her here in
Мы будем тут держать ону
short know your wife send
короче зн твою жену отпра
koby come on don’t Zelensky no
кобя давай не надо Зеленский не
less Excuse me for a second all people
зеле Извини меня на секундочку все люди
all the people, of course, are in Ukraine. Where did he
все люди конечно в Украине А куда он
go? Excuse me
свалил Извините меня
after the caliber arrives, I personally
после калибр прилетит я лично Зеленского
saw Zelensky, and last year they were bright
видел да в прошлом году яркой были
by the hand like that  I greeted him Yes, well,
у вот так за руку с ним здоровался Да ну
congratulations further wash Here again, but
поздравляю дальше помой Вот ещё раз но
you’re dad Yes, they won’t let you attract all these people now,
тебя папа Да они всех вот этих сейчас не
no Yes, you’ve already
дам тебе притянуть эту нет Да ты уже
attracted them because
притянула потому что
look, no, everyone will be
смотри смотри Нет все вот меня будут
watching me from the DPR, so the LPR,
смотреть из ДНР так лнр вот этих
they should see these occupied ones  Well,
оккупированных они должны видеть Да что
this Dad, he’s not like I’m not
вот этот Батя он не то что я же не
saying that he should have sent you to the front.
говорю что он тебя на фронт должен был
No, you said that, you said that,
отправить Да нет ты это и сказал ты это
and you said rewind. That’s what you said.
и сказал перемотай Вот ты это и сказал
Why is it giving up and he took you away?  in
Почему это Сдает а тебя он забрал в
Russia you didn’t stay in Donetsk Donetsk not
Россию ты не остался в Донецк Донецк не
on the line Donetsk not on the front line
на линии Донецк не на линии фронта
Why aren’t you sitting in
Почему ты не сидишь в
Donetsk in
Донецке в
Donetsk outside don’t look in
Донецке вне не смотри в
Donetsk you’re not captured but
Донецке тебя в плен не но
dad dad said that Listen let’s just let
папа папа сказал что Слушай давай так
these Yes for Russia like we are them  Let's have
эти Да за Россию типа мы их будем
mobile phones Yushka Yes my dear Yes with his
мобили Юшка Да мой родной Да со своей
wife Tanya Visit in Kostroma Yes I
женой танечкой Посетите в Костроме Да я
gave you an analogy about you doing
тебе аналогию приводил на вам тут делать
everything here Therefore he sings to the FSB that Therefore
всё Поэтому поёт к ФСБ что Поэтому
look also  since your child
смотри ещё раз так как твой ребёнок
will end up with the SBU if he is in Donetsk he is not on the
попадёт к СБУ если он в Донецке он не на
front line Tanyusha How are you doing
линии фронта Танюша Как там у тебя дела
she is great She is
у неё великолепно У неё
great she is already for you Say hi
великолепно она уже тебе Скажи привет
just yes Well just hello Yes you don’t
просто да Ну просто Привет Да не
have to show up Yes yes give me
обязательно показываться Да да дай
headphones let him
наушники пусть пусть онат
Hello Tanya, can you hear me, no, she
Привет Таня ты меня слышишь нет Она тебя
can’t hear you, you see everything, you’re afraid, like,
не слышит Всё наш видишь ты боишься типа
give her, of course, God forbid, she hears
дать ей конечно не дай бог она услышит
the truth from the Ukrainian, not for me, just, well,
правду из украинской не мне просто вот
give me headphones for a minute  to whom Well, Tanya
Ну дай на минуту наушники кому Ну Тане
Give me headphones for a minute, you won’t go Well,
Дай на минуту наушники не пойдёшь Ну
I’ll just say a few words to her and
просто я ей пару слов скажу и
don’t let your daughter wear them Well, she
всё не дай своей дочери науш Ну так она
came here and told you something, my
ж Пришла тут что-то говорила тебе моя
daughter doesn’t come here, I
дочь не приходит же тут
understand, wait Yeah, and now
понимаю подожди Ага и всё уже сейчас
you’ll get everything from
будешь получишь от
Tanka Okay, let me not shout
Таньки Ладно давай я не буду кричать
because now I need cabbage soup for my wife,
потому что мне сейчас уже жена щей надо
yes now I need cabbage soup for my wife.
да сейчас надо жена щей
Yes,
Да дай
God forbid, my wife realized that she smelled something fried
Бог всё жена поняла что жареным запахла
somewhere, maybe Alexey somewhere, how do you
гдето могут Алексею где-то как ты
come up with all this?  I find absolutely no
придумаешь это всё находу абсолютно не
arono, that is, I can say the same thing.
ароно то есть я могу То же самое
And by the way, excuse me,
говорить А между прочим Извини меня вот
this is a logical way out of the outcast. Wait, give me,
это ческий выход изго
yes, give me, Headphones, give me headphones,
Подожди дай Да дай дай Наушники дай
just let her not
наушники просто пусть она не
show up for the ninety-first year, everything is
показывается девяносто первый год всё
already
тебя уже
shorter
короче
in Yes
в Да
sniff, give
нюх дай
me, you'll
нюи ты
bypass the earphone.  It won't be Dan
обойдёшь наушник Не будет Дан
until cool cool buzz Kai here
до круто круто кайф Кай вот
I bombed you
сри я бомбанул тебя
I bombed you wa because look
я тебя ва потому что смотри Потому
Because Motorola you're not even  And what are these
что моторол ты даже не А что такое-то
two motorolas? Red, I said that he is from
два моторол Рыжий я сказал что он из
Slavyansk. I said that I might be
Славянска Я сказал что я могу быть
wrong, he is not from
неправ он не из
Slavyansk, we summarize,
Славянска мы резюмируем
yes, your
да твой
dad works for the Russian Federation. Yes,
батя работает на Российскую Федерацию
he is a collaborator, a citizen of the Russian
Да он коллаборант гражданин Российской
Federation, he is a Russian guy from
Федерации он парней из российской из
Donetsk and Lugansk. Yes.  sent you to
Донецка и Луганска Да Во тебя отправил в
Kostroma Yes with this little wife like yes
Кострому Да с этой жёнушка типа да вот
but I will say this the future I am a seer
но я скажу так будущее я вот я провидец
I see that your dad will remain in Donetsk
я вижу что твой батя останется в Донецке
you  you'll stay in
ты останешься в
Kostroma And your wife will live
Костроме А твоя жена будет жить
normally in Moscow with Mahmud Come on
нормально в Москве с махмудом Давай
Glory to Ukraine
Слава Украине
let's go to Instagram I don't know why
давай на й Instagram Я не знаю для чого
you should be amazed at the office and
це тоб для тоб там дивитись на офес а
for you there's one two or three clicks Ale
для тебе це один два або три клика Але
you trim me and I'll be there  Wow in me
ты тримае мене и я буду кти Вау в мене
there are a bunch of fouls and in me there will be a great
там Купа фолов и в мене буде класный
mood so that it’s robiti but cool video  write
настрий чтоб робити но крут видео пись
to th Instagram Popik Andriy
на й Instagram Попик Андрий
otak Dava u
отак Дава ю